Outlaws and Angels is a western, drama, thriller film directed by JT Mollner.
A gang of cold-blooded outlaws narrowly escapes a
blood-soaked bank robbery in a grimy frontier town.
With a notorious bounty hunter hot on their trail, these nefarious
criminals desperately need a place to hide out before night falls.
Fate brings them to the home of the Tildons, a seemingly
innocent family with two feisty daughters.
As the men settle in, an impetuous game of cat and mouse
plays out during the cold, black night.
Come morning, nothing will ever be the same.
Florence Tildon, played by Francesca Eastwood.
Henry, played by Chad Michael Murray.
Esther, played by Frances Fisher.
Ada Tildon, played by Teri Polo.
Josiah, played by Luke Wilson.
George Tildon, played by Ben Browder.
Outlaws and Angels is a 2016 American Western film written and directed by JT Mollner in his feature directorial
debut and starring Chad Michael Murray, Francesca Eastwood, Teri Polo, Frances Fisher and Luke Wilson.
The film received generally negative reviews from
critics and grossed $9,798 at the box office.
The film explores themes of bounty hunter, seduction, outlaw, revenge, gang.
The tone is emotional and intense.